Guide to the Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute RG.21.35
New York University Archives
Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute
1994-2015
New York University Archives
Geron, Tomio
Cabalda, Sheelagh
Morimoto, Risa
RG.21.35
32.75 Linear Feet in 30 boxes.
The records of the Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute, dated 1994-2015, document the activities of the Institute and reflect student events, faculty affairs and collaboration with the A/P/A studies program. The collection contains photographs, memoranda, correspondence, student surveys, meeting and conference agendas, syllabi, proposals, posters, flyers, and brochures. It also includes audio cassettes, VHS tapes, and mini DVs.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
These materials transferred to the University Archives in four accessions in 2008, 2009, 2010, and 2011.
Additional accretions were received in 2016 and 2017; the accession number associated with these transfers are 2016.024, 2016.029, and 2017.055.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches, and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
This collection contains audiovisual materials that have not been digitized. Please contact the University Archives if you wish to access these materials.
Please contact the University Archives with specific questions regarding restrictions.
History of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute
The Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute was founded in 1996. The Institute is focused on community and intercultural studies within a broad, rigorous international and comparative framework.
The A/P/A Institute produces public events and symposia for the larger New York University and New York City communities. The Institute brings together accomplished scholars, community builders, and artists from New York City and beyond for events throughout the year, including conferences, seminars, book readings, film screenings, musical performances, and brown bag lunches. The Institute also co-sponsors events with student and community organizations, which complement the academic programs offered by the University and address the needs of the community at large.
The A/P/A has collaborated on several events and activities with the Office for African American, Latino, and Asian American Student Services (OASIS). OASIS was created in 1988 in response to the expressed needs of students of color for more University administrative support and commitment. Today the mission of OASIS continues to be carried out by the Center for Multicultural Education and Programs (CMEP) at NYU.
The A/P/A Institute also reached out to youth in New York City through the Asian Pacific American Youth Alliance (APAYA) from 1994-2008. This was a free program led by A/P/A and community volunteers throughout the school year that sought to support and encourage high school youth to become community leaders. These students learned about and taught others about the vibrant and diverse Asian Pacific American history, cultures, and experiences. Their weekly meetings throughout the school year culminated in a forum at NYU planned and led by APAYA students.
Sources:
New York University. "Asian/Pacific/American Studies: The Institute." http://www.apa.nyu.edu
New York University. "Center for Multicultural Education and Programs: About Us." http://www.cmep.nyu.edu
New York University. "Asian/Pacific/American Institute: APAYA." http://www.nyu-apastudies.org/new/programs.php?type=apaya
Scope and Contents
The records of the Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute, dated 1994-2015, document the activities of the Institute from its founding in 1996 and reflect student events, faculty affairs and collaboration with the A/P/A studies program. The collection contains photographs, memoranda, correspondence, student surveys, meeting and conference agendas, syllabi, proposals, posters, flyers, and brochures. It also includes audio cassettes, VHS tapes, and mini DVs.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Syllabi.; Memorandums.; Photographs.; Administrative records.; Student activities.; New York (N.Y.); Posters.; Asian American college students.; New York University. Faculty of Arts and Science; New York University
- Series I: Conference, 726
  Access Restrictions
  Some personal information in this series has been restricted. Please contact the University Archives for details.
  Scope and Contents
  Series I contains information on the preparation and production of the Asians in America conference from 1994-1998, as well as other conferences of interest to the A/P/A community including Where is Home? Annual Conference for Chinese in the Americas, held in 1997 and Public Displays of Asianness, held in 1998. The records generally pertain to conference logistics, planning, and publicity.
  - Abstracts, 1995; 788 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abstracts, 1995-1996; 3025 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abstracts, 1997; 3026 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abstracts: Accepted, 1994-1995; 787 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Advertising and Publicity, 1995; 785 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advertising and Publicity, 1995; 784 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advertising and Publicity, 1996; 783 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advertising and Publicity, 1996; 782 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Advertising and Publicity, 2002; 181124 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Board, 2000; 781 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Asians in America Conference, 1995; 181409 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Asians in America Conference, 1996; 181410 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Budget, 1994-1995; 778 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Budget, 1995-1996; 777 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Budget, 1997; 3027 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Compendium Proposal, 1995; 775 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Contacts, 1994; 773 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995; 3028 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Development, 2000; 3029 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Diversity Resource Collaborative, 1996; 772 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Evaluation Forms, 1995; 771 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - General, 1995; 745 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - General, 1996; 744 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - General, 1997; 743 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - General, 1998; 742 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Logistics, 1995; 770 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Logistics, 1995; 769 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Logistics, 1996; 3030 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Logistics, 1996; 3031 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1994-1995; 767 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1995-1996; 766 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1995-1996; 3032 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Notes, 1995; 765 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 1997; 740 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Notes, 1999-2000; 3033 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Other Conferences, 1995; 763 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Other Conferences, 1996; 737 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Other Conferences, 1997-1998; 764 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Other Conferences, 1998; 3034 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Other Conferences, 1998; 3035 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Other Conferences, 1998; 3036 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Other Conferences, 1998-1999; 3037 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Panel: On Common Ground, 1996; 734 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Panelist Biographies, 1995; 762 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Panelist Biographies, 1996; 3038 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Panelist Biographies, 1997; 3039 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Papers, 1995-1996; 761 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Permissions, 2008; 181411 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Planning, 1994; 760 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Proceedings, 1996; 732 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Programs, 1995; 731 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Programs, 1997; 3040 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Publicity, 1997; 757 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Registration, undated; 756 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Registration, 1995; 754 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Registration, 1995; 3041 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Registration, 1996; 755 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Signage, 1997; 729 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Tasks, 1997; 728 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Volunteers, 2000; 727 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Volunteers and Committees, 1995-1996; 751 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Workshops, 1996; 750 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Where is Home? 5th Annual Conference for Chinese in the Americas - Registration, 1997; 162325 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Where is Home? 5th Annual Conference for Chinese in the Americas - Program, 1997; 162326 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Where is Home? 5th Annual Conference for Chinese in the Americas - Paid Registration, 1997; 162327 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Where is Home? 5th Annual Conference for Chinese in the Americas - Unpaid Registration, 1997; 162328 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Where is Home? 5th Annual Conference for Chinese in the Americas - Registration Forms, 1997; 162329 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Where is Home? 5th Annual Conference for Chinese in the Americas - Correspondence, 1997; 162330 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Why September 11?, 169257 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Asians In America - Meetings, 1998; 162331 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Asians In America - Event Planning, 1998; 162332 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Asians In America - Panels, 1998; 162333 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Asians In America - Youth Participants, 1998; 162334 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Asians In America - Agenda and Participants, 1998; 162335 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Public Displays of Asianness Conference - Registration, 1998; 162336 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Public Displays of Asianness Conference - Volunteers, 1998; 162337 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Public Displays of Asianness Conference - Insurance, 1998; 162338 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Public Displays of Asianness Conference - Participant Bios, 1998; 162339 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Public Displays of Asianness Conference - Emails, 1998; 162340 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Public Displays of Asianness Conference - Abstracts, 1998; 162341 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Public Displays of Asianness Conference - The Cooler, 1998; 162342 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Public Displays of Asianness Conference - Setup, 1998; 162343 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Series II: Administrative, 504
  Series II is divided into four subseries that relate to specific A/P/A staff members.
  - Subseries A: Sheelagh Cabalda, Office for African American, Latino and Asian American Student Services (OASIS), 162374
    Conditions Governing Access
    Some of the material within this subseries is restricted because it contains personal information. The physical folders within this collection that are restricted and the boxes have been marked.
    Subseries A contains records pertaining to Sheelagh Cabalda's work at the Office for African American, Latino and Asian American Student Services (OASIS) in collaboration with A/P/A. This subseries documents various conferences, workshops and events produced by OASIS, A/P/A and other institutions. These records provide an understanding of student activities and events related to A/P/A Institute.
    - AACU Community Seminars - Under One Roof, 1996-1997; 162344 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - AACU Community Seminars - Under One Roof, 1996-1997; 162345 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - AACU Diversity, Community & Intellectual Development, 1996; 162346 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - AACU Diversity, Community & Intellectual Development, 1996; 162347 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - African-American Services, 1997; 162348 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - American Museum of Natural History, undated; 162349 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - APA Administration/Faculty, 1998; 162351 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - APA Alums, 1997-1998; 162352 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - APA Events, 1999-2000; 162353 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - APA Info/Updates, 2000-2001; 162354 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - APA Retreat, 2001-2002; 162355 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - APA Semester Reports, 1999-2000; 162356 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - APA Studies Courses, 1997; 162357 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - APA Studies NYU Vision and Plan, undated; 162358 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - APA Studies Program, 169258 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - APA Studies Program Academic Year Report, 2000-2001; 162359 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - APASS, 1997-1998; 162360 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - APASS Retreat, 1998; 162361 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - APAYA, 2005; 162363 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - APAYA, 2005; 162364 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - APAYA Course, 2002-2003; 162365 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - APAYA Prep, 2004-2005; 162366 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - APAYA Prep, 2001-2002; 162367 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - APAYA/Workshop, Outlines, 2002; 162368 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - API Conference, 2003; 162369 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - API White House Iniative, 2000; 162375 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - API White House Iniative, 2000; 181126 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - APICHA Volunteer Training, 1995; 162376 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Articles (Miscellaneous), 1996-1998; 162377 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Asia in the Schools, undated; 162378 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Asia Pacific Conference on Student Affairs, 1996; 162379 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Asia Society, 2000; 162380 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Asian American Arts Alliance, 2002; 162381 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Asian American Arts Alliance Proposal, 2004; 162382 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Asian American Arts Organization, 1993; 162383 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - The Asian American Crisis, 1999; 162384 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Asian American Educators' Roundtable, 1997; 162436 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Asian American Identity Youth Forum, 2000; 162437 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Asian American Legal Defense Education Fund (AALDEF), 2001; 162438 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Studies, 1996-1997; 162439 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Studies Courses, 1996; 162440 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Asian American Writers' Workshop (AAWW), 2001; 162441 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Asian American Youth Forum, 2000; 162442 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Asian Americans in American Culture, 1996; 162443 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Asian Americans and War, undated; 162444 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Asian Heritage Month, 1996; 162445 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Asian New Student Orientation/Reception, 1995; 162446 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Asian Notes, 1996; 162447 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Asian Pacific American Journal Vol. 10, No. 2, 2002; 162448 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Asian Pacific American Student Services/CAS, 1996-1997; 162449 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Asian Pacific American Student Services/CAS, 1996-1997; 162450 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Asian and Pacific Americans in Higher Education (APACHE), 2002; 162451 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Asian Pacific Islander Coalition on HIV/AIDS, 2001; 162452 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Asian Professional Extension (APEX), undated; 162453 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Asian Stuff, 1992; 162454 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Asian Voices: Moments Vol. VIII, 1995; 162455 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Asian Voices: Moments Vol. X, 1997; 162456 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Asians in America, 2000; 162457 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Asians in America Youth ID Conference, 1999; 162458 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Audit of Violence Against Asian Pacific Americans, 2000; 162459 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - B/L/A Awards, 1996; 162460 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Bronx Museum, 2001; 162461 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Bronx Museum--Long-range planning, 2001; 162462 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Budget, 2001-2002; 162463 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Budget, 2002-2003; 162464 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Cammy Lee Foundation, 1999; 162465 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - CAPAY Newsletter, 2003; 162466 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Chinatown Manpower Project HS Intern, 2003; 162467 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Chinese Staff and Workers' Association, 2000; 162468 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Civil Rights, 1992-2003; 181412 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Clippings from The Nation, 2005; 162469 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Club dinners with Jack, 2003-2004; 162470 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Club Info, 1997-1998; 162471 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Cluster Campaign, 2003; 162472 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Community Organizations, 1999-2000; 162473 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Conferences, 1997-1999; 183366 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Conferences, 1997-1999; 162474 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence - Edward J. Sullivan, undated; 162475 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence - Space Rentals, 169265 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence - Thank You notes, 1995-2009; 162476 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence - Thank You notes, 1995-2009; 183367 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Co-Sponsorship, 2004-2005; 162477 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Counting Asian Americans, 2001; 162478 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Course Evaluations, 2003; 162479 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Course Tallies, 1997-2001; 162481 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Courses, 1998; 162482 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Courses, 2001; 162483 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Courses, 2002; 181141 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Courses, 2002-2005; 181142 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Course Listings - Spring 2005, 162480 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Crystal Music Productions, 1997; 162485 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - CSPA, undated; 162486 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Et Al, 1996-1998; 162487 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Cultural Information, 1999-2001; 162488 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Cultural Information, 1999-2001; 162489 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Dean's Rationale - A/P/A, 2003; 162493 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Deans - Students meeting on the status of NYU A/P/A studies within new interdisciplinary department, 2004; 162494 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Department of Social and Cultural Analysis, 2004; 162495 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Diversity Summit Teleconference, 1996; 162496 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Diversity Weekend, 1997-1998; 162497 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Diversity Workshop, undated; 162498 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - East Coast Asian Student Union 18th Annual Leadership Conference, 1996; 162500 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Education Roundtable, 2003-2004; 162502 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Educational/Cultural Programs, 1997-1998; 162503 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Educators' Roundtable, 2000; 162504 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - EIAA, 2005; 162506 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - EIAA, 2005; 162507 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Elementary Cantonese I, 1999; 162508 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Equal Multicultural Initative, 1999; 162509 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Et Al - Outreach Program Development Forms, 1996-1997; 162510 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Ethnography of Muslim Diaspora - Flyer, undated; 162511 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Events, 2003-2004; 162512 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Faces of America, 1996; 162513 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Facts, 1997-1998; 162514 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Fahsi Youth Day, 2003; 162515 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Focus Groups, 1996; 162516 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Focus Groups, 2003; 162517 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Food Conference, 2000; 162518 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - From Campus to Corporate, 2004; 162519 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Fundraising, 2000; 162520 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Gender Issues Weekend, 1992; 162521 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Gotham Center, 2001; 162522 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Healthcare, 182228 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Healthcare-Culturally Competent, 182229 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Impact of Inter-Cultural Conflict (draft), 1996; 162523 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Interdependent Study Focusing on Multiculturalism at NYU, 1999; 162524 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Interdependent Study Portfolio - Candice Uy, 2003; 162525 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Interdependent Study Portfolio - Candice Uy - Intern Projects, 2003; 162526 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Interdependent Study Portfolio - Candice Uy - Readings, 2003; 162527 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Interdependent Study Portfolio - Candice Uy - Presentation and Outline Headings, 2003; 162528 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - International Academic Credential Evaluation Guide, 1996; 162529 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - ISIP, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1997; 162530 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Japanese American National Museum, 2002; 162531 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Kishi Collection, 2001; 162532 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Leadership Institute, 1997-1998; 162534 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Life After NYU, undated; 162535 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Links Grant, 1997-1998; 162536 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Links Grant, 1997-1998; 162537 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Lists, undated; 162538 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Mailing Lists/Resource Guide, 1995-1997; 162539 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Manhattan Neighborhood Reniassance Local Development Corporation, 1996; 162540 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Mapping Project, 1999; 162541 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Mavin, Issue 7, undated; 162542 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - MOCADA Events, 2006; 162543 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Monolid Vol. 2, No. 2, undated; 162544 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Multicultural Leadership Weekend, 1997; 162545 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Mural Project - A/P/A Exhibit, 2003; 162546 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - National Asian Pacific American Political Almanac, 1998-1999; 162547 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - National Asian Pacific American Political Almanac, 1996; 162548 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 11th National Conference on Race & Ethnicity in Highter Education (NCORE), 1998; 162549 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - NEA - Asian American & Pacific Islander, 2005; 162550 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - New York Association for New Americans, Inc., 1995; 162551 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - NODA '97, 1997; 162552 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - OASIS Administration Search, 2004; 162553 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - OASIS/Focus Groups, 1997; 162554 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - OASIS Liasons, 2003-2004; 162555 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - OASIS Liasons Meeting, 2002; 162556 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Pacific Symposium, 2001; 162557 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Phati'tude, 1997; 162561 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Photocopying and Copyright, undated; 162562 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - The Public Theater, 1997; 162563 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - RealizAsian Vol. 1, No. 1, 1996; 162564 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - RealizAsian Vol. 1, No. 4, 1997; 162565 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Residence Hall Mailing, undated; 162567 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Residence Life Conference, 1996; 162568 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Response to 2001-02 Annual Planning Report, 162569 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - SCA Task Force, 182231 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Semester Reports, 1997-1998; 162570 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Share and Tell, 2004; 162571 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Small Event Fund Application, undated; 162572 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Social Services, 182232 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - South Asian America Comes of Age - Course, 1997; 162573 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - South Asian Studies Iniative, 2002-2003; 162574 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Student Leaders of Color, 1996; 162575 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Student Medialian Services, 1995; 162576 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Student Power Movement Ethnic Groups, undated; 162577 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Students of Color & Majors, 1999-2000; 162578 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Substance Abuse Committee, undated; 162579 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Summer Institute on Community Cultural Studies in NYC, 1997; 162580 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Surveys - OASIS, 1996; 162581 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Syllabi, 1998; 162582 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Syllabi, 1997; 162583 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Syllabi, 2000; 162584 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - A Teacher's Guide to Surviving and Thriving at A/P/A, 169253 (Box 13, Folder 53)